Copies
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Copies
2.1.1.1.32
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1255
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - View of ocean and mountains, before 1916; 14; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Boat near small island, before 1916; 15; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ocean, land in distance, before 1916; 16; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of sea and sky, land in distance, before 1916; 17; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean and mountains, before 1916; 18; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, land in distance, before 1916; 19; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, land in distance, before 1916; 20; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man taking picture of children near wall, before 1916; 21; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sheep in road, before 1916; 22; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Woman driving cart, before 1916; 23; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ocean and shore, before 1916; 24; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Children running near monument, before 1916; 25; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Mountains and ocean, before 1916; 26; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Looking towards forest and shore, before 1916; 27; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Loading people on small rowboats, before 1916; 28; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, land in distance, before 1916; 29; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man and two women, before 1916; 30; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Woman carrying basket on her back, before 1916; 31; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 32; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 33; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 34; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 35; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 36; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 37; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 38; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 39; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 40; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Three women carrying baskets, before 1916; 41; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man wearing hat, before 1916; 42; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Woman carrying basket on back, before 1916; 43; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Woman carrying basket on back, before 1916; 44; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sunset over ocean, before 1916; 45; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Automobile next to ship, before 1916; 46; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Woman squatting next to automobile, before 1916; 47; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Lifting automobile onto ship, before 1916; 48; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men standing next to cart, before 1916; 49; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - City skyline, before 1916; 50; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship deck, two men sitting in foreground, before 1916; 51; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of passengers on ship deck, before 1916; 52; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sailors sitting in lifeboats, before 1916; 53; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sailors climbing over railing into lifeboats, before 1916; 54; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship smokestack and deck, before 1916; 55; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of two officers on deck, before 1916; 56; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Smokestack, before 1916; 57; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on deck, looking over railing, before 1916; 58; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of passengers on ship deck, before 1916; 59; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers sitting on reclining chairs, before 1916; 60; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ship deck, before 1916; 61; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on deck, before 1916; 62; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ship deck, before 1916; 63; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sailors on lifeboat, before 1916; 64; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sailors climbing over railing into lifeboat, before 1916; 65; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ship deck, before 1916; 66; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Sailors sitting in lifeboat, before 1916; 67; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, from ship deck, before 1916; 68; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship deck, before 1916; 69; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Smokestack and ship deck, before 1916; 70; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of officer and deck, before 1916; 71; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Lifeboats and side of ship, before 1916; 72; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Distant view of ship, before 1916; 73; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of a boat, before 1916; 74; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on deck, looking over railing, before 1916; 75; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers seated on reclining chairs, before 1916; 76; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ocean from deck, before 1916; 77; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship deck and ocean, before 1916; 78; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on reclining chairs, before 1916; 79; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on deck, before 1916; 80; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers sitting in chairs, before 1916; 81; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ships, before 1916; 82; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship, before 1916; 83; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship, before 1916; 84; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship, passenger on deck, before 1916; 85; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man near railing, looking at ocean, before 1916; 86; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Lifting automobile onto ship, before 1916; 87; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Deck scene, before 1916; 88; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - View of ocean from ship deck, before 1916; 89; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ship deck, before 1916; 90; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, before 1916; 91; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Ocean, before 1916; 92; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, crowd watching, before 1916; 93; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, crowd watching, before 1916; 94; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, one falling off, crowd watching, before 1916; 95; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, crowd watching, before 1916; 96; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, one falling off, crowd watching, before 1916; 97; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Two men playing on rod, one falling off, crowd watching, before 1916; 98; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Group of children, before 1916; 99; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man wearing hat, close-up, before 1916; 100; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Man standing with donkey carrying bundles, before 1916; 101; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Old woman, before 1916; 102; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on ship, before 1916; 103; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on ship, before 1916; 104; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Passengers on ship, before 1916; 105; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Panorama of town, before 1916; 106; 3.5x6.75 film (Box 1255)
  - Panorama of factory, copy, before 1916; 107; 5x7 film (Box 1255)
  - Automobile in front of Sleepy Hollow Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1914 July 22; 108; 1; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Sleepy Hollow Bridge, donated by Rockefeller, Tarrytown, New York, 1914 July 22; 109; 2; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Church and road, Tarrytown, New York, before 1916; 110; 3; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Philipse Manor, Tarrytown, New York, 1914 July 22; 111; 4; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Entrance and park, Tuxedo, New York, 1914 July 23; 112; 12; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Church in park, Tuxedo, New York, 1914 July 23; 113; 13; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - George Washington Headquarters (Ford Mansion), Morristown, New Jersey, 1914 July 23; 114; 15; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Doorway and front of house, George Washington Headquarters, Morristown, New Jersey, 1914 July 23; 115; 16; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Morristown Golf Club, Morristown, New Jersey, 1914 July 24; 116; 19; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Mum[?] Avenue, street and automobile, East Orange, New Jersey, 1914 July 24; 117; 20; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Lawn and automobile, Mum[?] Avenue, East Orange, New Jersey, 1914 July 24; 118; 21; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Skyline of New York City, Before 1915; 119; 192; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Statue of Liberty in New York Harbor, before 1916; 120; 4x5 film (Box 1255)
  - Side view of Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 121; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, distant view, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 122; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 123; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - City-County Building, Temple Square, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 124; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - City-County Building, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 125; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 126; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah and City-County Building, distant view, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 127; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, side view, Salt Lake City, before 1916; 128; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, copy, before 1916; 129; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, copy, before 1916; 130; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Gateway, looking towards capital, Salt Lake City, before 1915; 131; 194; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Temple from temple grounds, Salt Lake City, before 1915; 132; 195; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Hotel Utah, Salt Lake City, before 1915; 133; 196; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Automobile under arch, California, before 1916; 134; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Close-up of automobile with four passengers, before 1916; 135; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - View of automobile and road, before 1915; 136; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Automobile on road lined with palm trees, before 1915; 137; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Automobile on road, before 1915; 138; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Two men in automobile, before 1915; 139; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  - Two automobiles on roadway, before 1915; 140; 5x7 (Box 1255)
  Box 1256
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Three people in automobile, before 1915; 1; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Automobiles in front of old building, before 1915; 2; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Looking down road lined with trees, before 1915; 3; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Automobile and road, before 1916; 4; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Palm trees, before 1916; 5; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Gate to Berkeley Square, before 1916; 6; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - People crossing land bridge, copy and Cliff Palace, Mesa Verde National Park, copy [split negative], before 1915; 7; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Lion head, done in Illinois, copy, 1915 December 13; 8; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Picture of Abraham Lincoln with quote, copy, 1913; 9; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Abraham Lincoln quote with portrait behind, copy, 1913; 10; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Abraham Lincoln quote, copy, 1913; 11; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Dog sled, copy for arctic lecture, before 1916; 12; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Large ship, copy for arctic lecture, 1909; 13; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Large ship in ice, copy for arctic lecture, 1909 October; 14; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Campsite, copy for arctic lecture, before 1916; 15; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Dining room, copy (South America), before 1916; 16; 11; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Cathedral, copy (South America), before 1916; 17; 12; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Bridge and river, church in distance, copy (South America), before 1916; 18; 15; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - View of city and mountains, copy (South America), before 1916; 19; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Three woman and a man, copy (South America), before 1916; 20; 52; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Two women sitting in front of building and gardens, copy (South America), before 1916; 21; 58; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Woman in serape, copy (South America), before 1916; 22; 62; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Stone wall and stream, copy (South America), before 1916; 23; 68; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Dock, copy (South America), before 1916; 24; 68; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - City and mountains, copy (South America), before 1916; 25; 80; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Trees and houses, copy (South America), before 1916; 26; 89; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Two men in suits, copy (South America), before 1916; 27; 100; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Trees, copy (South America), before 1916; 28; 188; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Church, Guayaquil, copy (South America), 1909 March 31; 29; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Tools, copy (South America), before 1916; 30; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Ship, copy (South America), before 1916; 31; 4x5 (Box 1256)
  - Street scene, South America, copy, before 1916; 32; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Railroad tracks in the mountains, South America, copy, before 1916; 33; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Man standing next to stone statue, South America, copy, before 1916; 34; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Temple, India, copy, before 1916; 35; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - People in masks, India, copy, before 1916; 36; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Temple, India, copy, before 1916; 37; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - The home ruler, the liveliest member in the house, copy, and the home ruler, a troublesome member when he likes, copy [split negative], before 1916; 38; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Two views of mountains and oceans, copy [split negative], before 1913; 39; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Stone statues, copy, before 1913; 40; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Road with trees, copy, before 1913; 41; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Stone statues, copy, before 1913; 42; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Road and trees, copy, before 1913; 43; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - View of city and bay, copy, before 1913; 44; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Rocks[?], copy, before 1913; 45; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Sailboats, copy, before 1913; 46; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Fried Krupp, copy, 1914 December 30; 47; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Field Marshall Lord Roberts, copy, German soldiers sharing food with Belgian orphans, copy, and sunset with Germans on guard, copy [split negative], 1914 December 30; 48; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Three German soldiers, New York Times, copy, 1914 December 30; 49; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Men sitting around table, before 1916; 50; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Ornate building and plants, copy, 1915 March 17; 51; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  - Cabin with large stone fireplace, before 1916; 52; 5x7 (Box 1256)
  Box 1257
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Arch overlooking ocean, before 1916; 1; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Street lined with cars, before 1916; 2; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Lake and forest, copy, before 1913; 3; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Mountains and valley, copy, before 1913; 4; ZZ; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Ships near shore, copy, and road through valley towards ocean, copy [split negative], before 1913; 5; NN; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Women at spinning wheel, copy, before 1913; 6; V; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Old woman at spinning wheel, copy, before 1913; 7; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Coming from the wood, copy, before 1913; 8; DD; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Women with large hats and men in suits, copy, before 1913; 9; EE; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Painting[?] of two people talking, copy, 1913; 10; 1X; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Three men on ship, before 1916; 11; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Room full of tables and chairs, copy, before 1916; 12; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Der Einsame, copy, 1910 July; 13; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of woman with child, copy, 1910 July; 14; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Prince Joachim, copy, and Prince Oscar, copy [split negative], before 1916; 15; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Two men rock climbing, copy, 1910 July; 16; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Rural home, street scene, copy, 1910 July; 17; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Town square, copy, 1910 July; 18; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Mountains, copy, 1910 July; 19; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Girl sitting by fountain, copy, 1910 July; 20; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Eiserne Jungfrau, copy, 1910 July; 21; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - People walking through streets, copy, 1910 July; 22; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - View of rooftops, copy, 1910 July; 23; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of men eating at table, copy, before 1916; 24; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Knight with a swan, copy, 1910 July; 25; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Men climbing mountain, copy, before 1916; 26; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Two men climbing mountain, copy, before 1916; 27; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Huge ship, copy, before 1916; 28; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Map of Northern Europe, copy, before 1916; 29; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of happy crowd, copy, 1910 July; 30; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Ornate room with chandelier, copy, 1910 July; 31; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Ornate room, copy, 1910 July; 32; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Old man sitting outside of tent, copy, before 1916; 33; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - View of mountains, river and valley, copy, Before 1913; 34; 5x7 (Box 1257)
  - Food stand, copy, before 1916; 35; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting[?] of man and stairs, copy, 1910 July; 36; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Woman in fancy dress with feathered hat, copy, before 1916; 37; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Cattle, copy, before 1913; 38; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Woman in fancy dress, copy, before 1913; 39; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Little girl in bonnet, copy, before 1913; 40; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Pod of whales, before 1916; 41; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Sheep, copy, before 1913; 42; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Sunset over the ocean and mountains, copy, before 1913; 43; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Cave, copy, before 1916; 44; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - River and mountains, copy, before 1916; 45; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of a dog, copy, before 1916; 46; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Passengers looking over ship railing, before 1913; 47; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Arch looking over ocean, copy, before 1916; 48; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Palm trees, copy, before 1916; 49; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Man in suit and fez, copy, before 1916; 50; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Man in military uniform, copy, before 1916; 51; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Two boys and a girl, copy, before 1916; 52; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Man in military uniform, copy, before 1916; 53; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Street lined with automobiles, copy, before 1916; 54; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Men sitting around table, copy, before 1916; 55; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of saints with Jesus, copy, 1910 July; 56; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Painting of woman with two babies, copy, 1910 July; 57; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - People near wooden fence, 1913; 58; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  - Street scene, copy, 1913; 59; 21X; 4x5 (Box 1257)
  Box 1258
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Large building with statue on roof, copy, 1913; 1; 22X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Large building, copy, 1913; 2; 23X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Statue of a lion, copy, 1913; 3; 18X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Marie Antoinette in the Conciergerie, copy, before 1916; 4; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Street scene, copy, before 1916; 5; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Rooftops, copy, 1910 July; 6; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Street scene, copy, 1914; 7; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Interior of cathedral, copy, 1910 July; 8; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Street and buildings, copy, 1910 July; 9; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Band, in uniform, copy, 1910 July; 10; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - City rooftops, copy, 1910 July; 11; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Painting of an angel, copy, 1910 July; 12; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Ornate room with chandelier, copy, 1910 July; 13; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Throne room, copy, 1910 July; 14; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Staircase landing, copy, before 1916; 15; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Sitting room, copy, before 1916; 16; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Military officers, copy, before 1916; 17; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Woman and children, copy, before 1916; 18; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Ornately carved house, copy, before 1914; 19; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - View of city, copy, before 1914; 20; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Two old men, copy, before 1914; 21; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - View of street, copy, before 1914; 22; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Gate, copy, before 1916; 23; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Hole in roof of house, copy, before 1916; 24; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Peasants carrying pails, copy, before 1914; 25; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Man and woman with accordion, copy, before 1914; 26; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - View down street, copy, 1913; 27; 19X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Ornate building, copy, 1913; 28; 17X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - View down street, copy, 1913; 29; 16X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - View of rooftops, copy, before 1914; 30; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Men and horses, copy, before 1914; 31; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Women and children, copy, before 1914; 32; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Two women with wheat, copy, before 1914; 33; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Crocodile, before 1916; 34; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Pen full of crocodiles, before 1916; 35; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Boy sitting on crocodile (Chase negative), before 1915; 36; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Headshot of boy, copy, before 1916; 37; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - William T. Noble, before 1913; 38; 4x5 film (Box 1258)
  - Ship in storm, copy, before 1913; 39; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Ship, copy, before 1916; 40; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Rocks and ocean, copy, before 1916; 41; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Painting of man in crown with lantern, copy, before 1916; 42; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Ship on the rocks, copy, before 1913; 43; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Painting of woman, baby and two men, copy, before 1913; 44; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Man in suit, copy, before 1913; 45; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Sunset, copy, before 1913; 46; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Statue of woman, copy, before 1913; 47; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Painting of woman with dog, copy, before 1913; 48; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Sunset, copy, before 1913; 49; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Shelves of skulls, before 1916; 50; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Chopin, copy, 1913; 51; 47X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Adam de Wieniawski, copy, 1913; 52; 46X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Old man, copy, 1913; 53; 37X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Woman in fancy hat, copy, 1913; 54; 29X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Old man with long beard, copy, 1913; 55; 40X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Man and woman in traditional costumes, copy, before 1914; 56; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Old man, copy, before 1916; 57; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Man with scraggly beard, copy, 1913; 58; 39X; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Old woman, copy, 1910 July; 59; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  - Woman in traditional costume, copy, 1910 July; 60; 4x5 (Box 1258)
  Box 1259
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Man and woman in traditional costumes, copy, 1910 July; 1; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Woman with wild hair, copy, 1913; 2; 43X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Man in suit, copy, before 1916; 3; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Woman in dress, copy, before 1916; 4; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Man and woman in traditional costumes, copy, 1910 July; 5; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Woman in traditional costume, copy, 1910 July; 6; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Ornate hall, copy, 1910 July; 7; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting[?] of women with children, copy, 1910 July; 8; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Two men and woman in traditional costumes, copy, 1910 July; 9; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Man sitting at table, copy, before 1914; 10; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Man in traditional costume with sword, copy, before 1914; 11; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Soldier on horse in front of grave, copy, 1913; 12; 34X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - People in horse drawn chariot, copy, 1913; 13; 35X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - View of street and large building, copy, 1913; 14; 20X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Train depot, copy, before 1916; 15; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Automobiles in front of building, copy, before 1916; 16; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Church, copy, before 1916; 17; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Ornate building, copy, before 1916; 18; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - The Sultan of Turkey, copy, before 1916; 19; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Ornate hall, copy, 1910 July; 20; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Bedchamber, copy, 1910 July; 21; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Long hallway, copy, before 1916; 22; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting of women, baby and rabbit, copy, 1910 July; 23; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting of women and baby, copy, 1910 July; 24; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting of a man, copy, 1910 July; 25; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting of woman and angels, copy, 1910 July; 26; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Painting of woman and babies, copy, 1910 July; 27; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Sleeping car compartment, copy, before 1916; 28; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - A sleeping car compartment arranged for the night, copy, before 1916; 29; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Extraordinary bronze incense burner, copy, 1914 January; 30; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Ship near the shore, copy, before 1916; 31; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Paul Kochanski, copy, 1913; 32; 32X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Two naked women, copy, 1913; 33; 33X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Man with messy hair, copy, 1913; 34; 36X; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  - Flower in vase on chair, before 1916; 35; 3.5 x 6 film (Box 1259)
  - Flowers in field, before 1916; 36; 3.5 x 6 film (Box 1259)
  - Flowers, before 1916; 37; 3.5 x 6 film (Box 1259)
  - Flowers and log, before 1916; 38; 3.5 x 6 film (Box 1259)
  - Flowers and log, before 1916; 39; 4.5 x 3.5 film (Box 1259)
  - Boy in sailor uniform, Russia, 40; 4x5 (Box 1259)
  Box 1260
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Flowers, before 1916; 1; 0983; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Flowers [broken], before 1916; 2; 0984; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Explosion, Panama, before 1916; 3; 0985; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Canal, copy, a typical family of Chorrera Panama, copy, and a doorstep scene, copy [split negative], before 1916; 4; 0986; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Flag of Poland, before 1914; 5; 0987; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)